A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 100 International - Series 253 Washington FA387a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Texas, 1947-1965; 249; 1.2 Cubic Feet; 3 __Boxes __1.2 cubic feet
  - Texas - Natural Sciences, 249.D
    - University of Texas - Cytogenetics - (Drosophila Studies, T.J. Patterson), 1949-1953, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - University of Texas - Gene Chemistry - (Pattersonm J. T), 1947-1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - University of Texas - Gene Chemistry - (Pattersonm J. T), 1947-1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - University of Texas - Gene Chemistry - (Pattersonm J. T), 1947-1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - University of Texas - Gene Chemistry - (Pattersonm J. T), 1947-1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - University of Texas - Gene Chemistry - (Pattersonm J. T), 1947-1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - University of Texas - Gene Chemistry - Reprints, 1954, 1957-1961; 40 Items (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - University of Texas - Gene Chemistry - Reports, 1951, 1955; 2 Items (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Washington, 1947-1950; 253; 0.4 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
  One subseries as follows: 253 R Humanities and arts
  - Washington - Humanities and Arts, 1947-1950; 253.R; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
    - University of Washington - Rader, Melvin - (Philosophy), 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)